Parmvir Singh

213 South Park Drive, Ilford, IG3 9AJ, England, UK +44 7466 355656
Parmvi67@gmail.com

Personal Statement

A hard working, enthusiastic and motivated individual. Who enjoys learning new skills and further developing previously gained skills. The ability to work independently and as part of a team. Experienced and comfortable operating multiple heavy machinery such as: Excavator, Folk Lift Trucks, Wheel Loader etc.

Employment History

Diamond Limit

Bricklayer

- Undertake building and repair work
- Maintain a high standard in every job
- Throughly check after completion that the job is to the company standard

Rkesa Ltd - Lisboa, Portugal

May 2017 - 20 December 2019

January 2020 - Present

Industrial Climber, Builder, Painter and Window Cleaner

- Undertake building and repair work
- Painting to a high quality
- Window cleaning when required including high buildings

Break between employment was to go India for a long vacation and visit family

First Kuwaity - Kuwait, Kuwait

Heavy Machinery Operator

- Wheel loader (Shovel loading)
- JCB 3CX backhoe loader
- Folk lift truck
- Excavator

Education & Qualifications

Senior Secondary School, Kapurthala

References

Are available on request

December 2012 - October 2016